Guide to the Northwest Horticultural Council Records 1953-1977
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1.2: Topical Files
    - Subseries 1.2.3: 1976-1977
      - Bills Paid - NHC, 1976-1977; 44 items. (Box 7, Folder 248)
      - Board of Trustees - NHC, 1976-1977; 67 items. (Box 7, Folder 249)
      - Board of Trustees - NHC, 1976-1977; 29 items. (Box 7, Folder 250)
      - California Grape and Tree Fruit League, 1976-1977; 27 items. (Box 7, Folder 251)
      - California State Regulations, 1976-1977; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 252)
      - Cash Disbursements - NHC, 1976-1977; 11 items. (Box 7, Folder 253)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 7, Folder 254)
      - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S., 1976-1977; 23 items. (Box 7, Folder 255)
      - Cherries, 1976-1977; 47 items. (Box 7, Folder 256)
      - Cherries, 1975-1976; 59 items. (Box 7, Folder 257)
      - Congressional Correspondence, 1976-1977; 81 items. (Box 7, Folder 258)
      - Congressman Foley Meeting, 1976-1977; 36 items. (Box 7, Folder 259)
      - Council of Fruit and Vegetable Association Executives, 1976-1977; 46 items. (Box 7, Folder 260)
      - Drought in the Yakima Valley, 1976-1977; 9 items. (Box 7, Folder 261)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 64 items. (Box 7, Folder 262)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 75 items. (Box 7, Folder 263)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 66 items. (Box 7, Folder 264)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 49 items. (Box 7, Folder 265)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticides, 1976-1977; 78 items. (Box 7, Folder 266)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticides, 1976-1977; 67 items. (Box 7, Folder 267)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticides, 1976-1977; 44 items. (Box 7, Folder 268)
      - Envorinmental Protection Agency-Northwest Committee for a Sensible Pesticide Policy, 1976-1977; 36 items. (Box 7, Folder 269)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Federal Register, 1976-1977; 56 items. (Box 7, Folder 270)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 68 items. (Box 7, Folder 271)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticides-Occupational Safety, 1976-1977; 79 items. (Box 7, Folder 272)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticides, 1976-1977; 47 items. (Box 7, Folder 273)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Pesticide Re-registration, 1976-1977; 81 items. (Box 7, Folder 274)
      - Environmental Protection Agency-Supplemental, 1976-1977; 7 items. (Box 8, Folder 275)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977; 9 items. (Box 8, Folder 276)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action, 1976-1977; 3 items. (Box 8, Folder 277)
      - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 8, Folder 278)
      - Falk, Ernest, 1976-1977; 26 items. (Box 8, Folder 279)
      - Falk, Ernest, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 8, Folder 280)
      - Farm Labor, 1976-1977; 64 items. (Box 8, Folder 281)
      - Farm Labor Contractor Registration Act, 1976-1977; 79 items. (Box 8, Folder 282)
      - Farm Labor - Housing, 1976-1977; 71 items. (Box 8, Folder 283)
      - Farm Labor Legislation, 1976-1977; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 284)
      - Farm Labor Legislation, 1976-1977; 168 items. (Box 8, Folder 285)
      - Farm Labor Unionization, 1976-1977; 6 items. (Box 8, Folder 286)
      - Farm Labor Unionization-Yakima Valley, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 287)
      - Federal Trade Commission, 1976-1977; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 288)
      - Food and Drug Act, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 289)
      - Food and Drug Act Regulations, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 290)
      - Grades and Standards, Apple and Pear, 1976-1977; 5 items. (Box 8, Folder 291)
      - Grades and Standards, Apple and Pear, Other States, 1976-1977; 26 items. (Box 8, Folder 292)
      - Grapes, 1976-1977; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 293)
      - Hop Growers of America, 26 items. (Box 8, Folder 294)
      - International Apple Institute, 78 items. (Box 8, Folder 295)
      - League of Women Voters of Yakima County, 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 296)
      - Mexican Nationals: Migratory Workers, 187 items. (Box 8, Folder 297-300)
      - United States Department of Labor Hearings, 5 items. (Box 8, Folder 301)
      - National Council of Agricultural Employers, 202 items. (Box 8, Folder 302-304)
      - National Labor Relations Act, 1976-1977; 3 items. (Box 8, Folder 305)
      - National Legislation, 1976-1977; 27 items. (Box 8, Folder 306)
      - National Legislation-Employment of Aliens, 1976-1977; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 307)
      - Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, 1976-1977; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 308)
      - Occupational Health Standards: Washington, 1976-1977; 8 items. (Box 8, Folder 309)
      - Oregon Horticultural Society, 1976-1977; 5 items. (Box 8, Folder 310)
      - Oregon-Washington-California Pear Bureau, 1976-1977; 46 items. (Box 8, Folder 311)
      - Oregon-Washington-Califonia Trade Bureau, 1976-1977; 6 items. (Box 8, Folder 312)
      - Pacific Coast Deciduous Fruit Council, 1976-1977; 7 items. (Box 8, Folder 313)
      - Pacific Coast Deciduous Fruit Council, 1976-1977; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 314)
      - Pacific Legal Foundation, 1976-1977; 24 items. (Box 8, Folder 315)
      - Packaging and Labeling Restrictions, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 316)
      - Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 8, Folder 317)
      - Pollution, 1976-1977; 5 items. (Box 8, Folder 318)
      - Prices and Costs, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 319)
      - Research Commission, 1976-1977; 44 items. (Box 8, Folder 320)
      - Resumes, 1976-1977; 6 items. (Box 8, Folder 321)
      - School Lunch, 1976-1977; 43 items. (Box 8, Folder 322)
      - School Lunch, 1976-1977; 29 items. (Box 8, Folder 323)
      - School Lunch, 1976-1977; 26 items. (Box 8, Folder 324)
      - Spray: Organic, 1976-1977; 7 items. (Box 8, Folder 325)
      - Traffic Association Trust Fund, 1976-1977; 10 items. (Box 8, Folder 326)
      - Trustees Meeting-Agenda Item, 1976-1977; 7 items. (Box 8, Folder 327)
      - Unemployment Compensation for Farm Workers, 1976-1977; 23 items. (Box 8, Folder 328)
      - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Assoc., 1976-1977; 26 items. (Box 8, Folder 329)
      - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Assoc. Government Relations, 1976-1977; 34 items. (Box 8, Folder 330)
      - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Assoc., 1976-1977; 77 items. (Box 8, Folder 331)
      - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Assoc, 1976-1977; 66 items. (Box 8, Folder 332)
      - United Political Action Committee, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 8, Folder 333)
      - United States Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 334)
      - United States Department of Agriculture, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1977; 54 items. (Box 9, Folder 335)
      - United States Department of Commerce, 1976-1977; 20 items. (Box 9, Folder 336)
      - United States Departments of State and Labor, 1976-1977; 35 items. (Box 9, Folder 337)
      - Washington State Apple Commission, 1976-1977; 40 items. (Box 9, Folder 338)
      - Washington State Commission Merchants Act, 1976-1977; 17 items. (Box 9, Folder 339)
      - Washingon State Department of Agriculture, 1976-1977; 23 items. (Box 9, Folder 340)
      - Washington State Department of Agriculture, 1976-1977; 9 items. (Box 9, Folder 341)
      - Washington State Department of Commerce, 1976-1977; 67 items. (Box 9, Folder 342-344)
      - Washington State Department of Health, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 345)
      - Washington State Department of Employment Security, 1976-1977; 59 items. (Box 9, Folder 346)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, 22 items (Box 9, Folder 347-348)
      - Washington State Horticultural Association, 1976-1977; 48 items. (Box 9, Folder 349)
      - Washington State Legislation, 1976-1977; 11 items. (Box 9, Folder 350)
      - Washington Women For the Survival of Agriculture, 1976-1977; 18 items. (Box 9, Folder 351)
      - Wenatchee Valley Traffic Association, 1976-1977; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 352)
      - Western International Trade Group, 1976-1977; 62 items. (Box 9, Folder 353)
      - Winter Pear Control Correspondence, 1976-1977; 46 items. (Box 9, Folder 354)
      - Witholding Tax, 1976-1977; 95 items. (Box 9, Folder 355-356)
      - Yakima Valley Growers-Shippers Association, 1976-1977; 24 items. (Box 9, Folder 357)
      - Yakima Valley Nursery, 1976-1977; 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 358)
- Series 2: Exports
  - Subseries 2.1: 1971-1975
    - Anti-dumping Duties, 75 items. (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Hearings, 50 items. (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Hearings, 25 items. (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Hearings, 15 items. (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Apple and Pear Export, 33 items. (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Apple Subsidy, 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - California - Arizona Citrus Industry, 24 items. (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Canadian Regulations, 5 items. (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Canadian Regulations, 14 items. (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Canadian Tariff, 10 items. (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - European Common Market, 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - European Common Market, 11 items. (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - European Representatives: Accounts, 35 items. (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - European Representatives: Accounts, 3 items. (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - European Representatives: Accounts, 20 items. (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - European Representatives: Accounts, California Grapes, 71 items. (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - California Grapes, 38 items. (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - California Grapes, 25 items. (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Caribbean, Latin America: Brazil Promotion, 38 items. (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - Brazil Promotion, 30 items. (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Brazil Promotion, 21 items. (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Cooperative Billing, 18 items. (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Cooperative Billing, 26 items. (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Cooperative Billing, Correspondence, 70 items. (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Correspondence, 55 items. (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Correspondence, 113 items. (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Correspondence, Disbursement, 7 items. (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Correspondence, 37 items. (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Correspondence, 4 items. (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Financial Reports, 14 items. (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Financial Reports, 12 items. (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Financial Representatives, 19 items. (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Financial Representatives, 29 items. (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Financial Representatives, 9 items. (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Financial Representatives, Work Plan, Marketing Plan, 20 items. (Box 11, Folder 393)
    - Work Plan, Marketing Plan, 8 items. (Box 11, Folder 394)
    - Work Plan, Marketing Plan, 19 items. (Box 11, Folder 395)
    - Finland, 26 items. (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Foreign Agricultural Service, 30 items. (Box 11, Folder 397)
    - Foreign Agricultural Service, 19 items. (Box 11, Folder 398)
    - Foreign Trade Policy, 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - France, 10 items. (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs, 46 items. (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs, 3 items. (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - General Agreement on Traffic and Trade, 6 items. (Box 11, Folder 403)
    - Germany, 6 items. (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Imports, 4 items. (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - Japan, 12 items. (Box 11, Folder 406)
    - Latin America, 79 items. (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Mexico, 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 408)
    - Middle East, 9 items. (Box 11, Folder 409)
    - Mission to Europe: Reports, 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Mission to Europe: Reports, 50 items. (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Mission to Europe: Reports, 51 items. (Box 11, Folder 412)
    - Other European Countries, 8 items. (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Pacific Area: Hong Kong, Philippines, Taiwan, 4 items. (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Palletizing, 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Port of Seattle, 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Quarantine Regulations, Moth, 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Quarantine Regulations, Moth, Australian and Tasmanian Apples, 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Southern Hemisphere, 9 items. (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 7 items. (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Special Representative, Trade Policy, 14 items. (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Subsidies, 5 items. (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Sweden, 25 items. (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Trade Reform Act of 1973, 41 items. (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Trade Reform Act of 1973, 9 items. (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - United Kingdom, 14 items. (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - United States-Canada Meetings, 6 items. (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - International Trade Commission, 30 items. (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - International Trade Commission, 17 items. (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Fruit Export Council, 14 items. (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Fruit Export Council, 28 items. (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Winter Pears: Klahre Study, 5 items. (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Subseries 2.2: 1975-1976
    - Anti-Dumping Duties, 18 items. (Box 12, Folder 433)
    - Apple and Pear Export, 77 items. (Box 12, Folder 434)
    - California-Arizona Citrus Industry, 45 items. (Box 12, Folder 435)
    - Canadian Regulations, 82 items. (Box 12, Folder 436)
    - Canadian Regulations, Tariff, 6 items. (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Domestic-International Sales Corporation, 7 items. (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - European Common Market, 67 items. (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - European Common Market Promotion, 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - European Common Market Representative, 26 items. (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - European Common Market Representative - California Grapes, 93 items. (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - European Common Market - Caribbean, Latin American Promotion, Brazilian Promotion
      - Cooperator Billing, 86 items. (Box 12, Folder 445)
      - Cooperator Billing Correspondence, 191 items. (Box 12, Folder 446-448)
      - Disbursements, Financial Reports, 56 items. (Box 12, Folder 449)
      - Financial Reports, Long-Range Market Development, 36 items. (Box 12, Folder 450)
      - Long-Range Market Development Reports, 62 items. (Box 12, Folder 451)
      - Long-Range Market Development Reports, Work and Marketing Plan, 54 items. (Box 12, Folder 452)
    - Export: France, 23 items. (Box 12, Folder 453)
    - Export: Finland, 26 items. (Box 12, Folder 454)
    - Export: Germany, 24 items. (Box 12, Folder 455)
    - Export: Japan, 21 items. (Box 12, Folder 456)
    - Export: Latin America, 47 items. (Box 12, Folder 457)
    - Export: Mexico, 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 458)
    - Export: Middle East, 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 459)
    - Export: Other European Countries, 29 items. (Box 12, Folder 460)
    - Export: Pacific Area, 27 items. (Box 12, Folder 461)
    - Export: Southern Hemispere, 29 items. (Box 12, Folder 462)
    - Export: Sweden, 72 items. (Box 12, Folder 463)
    - Export: United Kingdom, 32 items. (Box 12, Folder 464)
    - Export: Foreign Agricultural Service, 25 items. (Box 12, Folder 465)
    - Export: Foreign Agricultural Service, Market Development Projects, 56 items. (Box 12, Folder 466)
    - Export: Market Development Projects, Trade Policy, 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 467)
    - General Agreement on Trade And Tariffs, 17 items. (Box 12, Folder 468)
    - General Agreement on Trade And Tariffs, 12 items. (Box 12, Folder 469)
    - Imports, Miscellaneous, 16 items. (Box 12, Folder 470)
    - International Trade Commission, 20 items. (Box 12, Folder 471)
    - Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 23 items. (Box 12, Folder 472)
    - Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 44 items. (Box 12, Folder 473)
    - Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 55 items. (Box 12, Folder 474)
    - Subsidies, 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 475)
    - United States Fruit Export Council, 9 items. (Box 12, Folder 476)
  - Subseries 2.3: 1976-1977
    - Apple and Pear Export, 81 items. (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - California-Arizona Citrus Industry, 36 items. (Box 13, Folder 478)
    - Canadian Regulations, 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 479)
    - Canadian Tariff, 17 items. (Box 13, Folder 480)
    - Domestic International Sales Corporation, 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 481)
    - European Common Market
      - General, 19 items. (Box 13, Folder 482)
      - Promotion, 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 483)
      - Representative, 36 items. (Box 13, Folder 484)
      - Account and Savings, 21 items. (Box 13, Folder 485)
      - California Grapes, 45 items. (Box 13, Folder 486-487)
      - Cooperator Billing, Travel Reports, 37 items. (Box 13, Folder 488)
      - Correspondence, 45 items. (Box 13, Folder 489)
      - Financial Reports, 20 items. (Box 13, Folder 490)
      - Financial Reports, 14 items. (Box 13, Folder 491)
      - Financial Reports, Long-Range Plans, 18 items. (Box 13, Folder 492)
      - Financial Reports, 38 items. (Box 13, Folder 493)
      - Financial Reports, Marketing Plan, 56 items. (Box 13, Folder 494)
      - Marketing Plan, Promotion Material, 74 items. (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - Export: Finland, 23 items. (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - Export: France, 8 items. (Box 13, Folder 497)
    - Export: Germany, 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - Export: Japan, 17 items. (Box 13, Folder 499)
    - Export: Japan, 76 items. (Box 13, Folder 500)
    - Export: Latin America, 87 items. (Box 13, Folder 501)
    - Export: Mexico, 18 items. (Box 13, Folder 502)
    - Export: Midlle East, 8 items. (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - Export: Other European, 26 items. (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - Export: Pacific Area, 57 items. (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Export: South America, 24 items. (Box 13, Folder 506)
    - Export: Southern Hemisphere, 37 items. (Box 13, Folder 507)
    - Export: Sweden, 23 items. (Box 13, Folder 508)
    - Export: United Kingdom, 7 items. (Box 13, Folder 509)
    - Foreign Agricultural Service, 230 items. (Box 13, Folder 510)
    - Foreign Market Development, 54 items. (Box 13, Folder 511)
    - Foreign Market Development Trade Policy, 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 512)
    - Imports, Miscellaneous, 5 items. (Box 13, Folder 513)
    - International Trade Commission, 47 items. (Box 13, Folder 514)
    - Italy: Apple Production, 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 515)
    - Special Representative For Trade Negotiations, 45 items. (Box 13, Folder 516)
    - Trade Policy Staff, 67 items. (Box 13, Folder 517)
    - Trade Policy Staff, 53 items. (Box 13, Folder 518)
    - Trade Negotiations, Multilateral, 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 519)
    - Trade Negotiations, Multilateral, 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 520)
    - United States National Fruit Export Council, 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 521)
    - Winter Pears, 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 522)
- Series 3: Transportation
  - Subseries 3.1: 1972-1975
    - Apple and Pear Export, 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Ex Parte 241, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Ex Parte 256-296, 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Ex Parte 288, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Ex Parte 288, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Ex Parte 295, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Ex Parte 295, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 529)
    - Ex Parte 299, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 530)
    - Ex Parte 300, 29 items. (Box 14, Folder 531)
    - Ex Parte 300, 14 items. (Box 14, Folder 532)
    - Ex Parte 300, 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 533)
    - Ex Parte 300, 30 items. (Box 14, Folder 534)
    - Ex Parte 300, 25 items. (Box 14, Folder 535)
    - Ex Parte 303, 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Ex Parte 301-05, 19 items. (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Ex Parte 305, 25 items. (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Ex Parte 310, 26 items. (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Ex Parte 313, 12 items. (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - Ex Parte 314, 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 541)
    - Freight Rates, 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 542)
    - Highway Users Conference, 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - Increased Linehaul, 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 544)
    - Interstate Commerce, 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 545)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Service
      - Orders, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 546)
      - Docket 35431, 25 items. (Box 14, Folder 547-549)
      - Docket 8944, 173 items. (Box 14, Folder 549-551)
    - Mechanical Refrigeration Cars, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 552)
    - National Fruit and Vegetable Claims Committee, 12 items. (Box 14, Folder 553)
    - National Fruit and Vegetable Claims Committee, 15 items. (Box 14, Folder 554)
    - Ocean Rates
      - North Atlantic Conference, 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 555)
      - Pacific Coast Conference, 94 items. (Box 14, Folder 556)
      - European Conference, 38 items. (Box 14, Folder 557)
      - Westbound Conference, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 558)
      - South American-Latin American Conference, 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 559)
      - Latin American Conference, 24 items. (Box 14, Folder 560)
      - Latin American Conference, 26 items. (Box 14, Folder 561)
    - Pacific Northwest Freight Rate Group, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 562)
    - Pacific Northwest Freight Rate Group, 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 563)
    - Railroad Conference, 7 items. (Box 14, Folder 564)
    - Refrigerator Car Supply, 8 items. (Box 14, Folder 565)
    - Sunkist Complaint versus Railroad, 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 566)
    - Tolan, Fred H., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 567)
    - Transcontinental Freight Bureau Applications, 38 items. (Box 14, Folder 568)
    - Transportation Committee, 64 items. (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - Transportation Committee, 30 items. (Box 14, Folder 570)
    - Transportation Committee, 62 items. (Box 14, Folder 571)
    - Legislation, 22 items. (Box 15, Folder 572)
    - Truck Brokers, 7 items. (Box 15, Folder 573)
    - Truck Brokers, 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 574)
    - Trucks and Exempt Carriage, 8 items. (Box 15, Folder 575)
    - United Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Association, 19 items. (Box 15, Folder 576)
    - Washington Utilities and Transportation, 23 items. (Box 15, Folder 577)
  - Subseries 3.2: 1975-1976
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 303, 56 items. (Box 16, Folder 578)
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 303, 58 items. (Box 16, Folder 579)
    - Ex Parte 256-299 and 301-305: Fuel Surcharge, 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 580)
    - Ex Parte 301-305: Fuel Surcharge, 24 items. (Box 16, Folder 581-582)
    - >Ex Parte 301-305: Seven Percent Rail Increase, Petitions, 118 items. (Box 16, Folder 583-585)
    - Ex Parte 313: Five Percent Increase, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 586)
    - Ex Parte 318: Seven Percent Increase, 8 items. (Box 16, Folder 587)
    - Highway Users Conference: Washington and National, 4 items. (Box 16, Folder 588)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
      - Miscellaneous, 5 items. (Box 16, Folder 589)
      - Service Orders, 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 590)
    - Investigation and Suspension Docket, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 591)
    - Investigation and Suspension Docket, #8944, Court Case, 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 592)
    - Investigation and Suspension Docket, #8944, Increased Freight Rates, 36 items. (Box 16, Folder 593)
    - Mechanical Refrigerator Cars, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 594)
    - National Container Committee
      - Uniform Classification, 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 595)
      - Fruit and Vegetable Claims Committee, 43 items. (Box 16, Folder 596)
      - Perishable Freight Committee, 40 items. (Box 16, Folder 597)
    - Ocean: Intermodal, 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 598)
    - Ocean Rates
      - North Atlantic Conference, 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 599)
      - Pacific Coast European Conference, 32 items. (Box 16, Folder 600)
      - Pacific Coast European Conference, 28 items. (Box 16, Folder 601)
      - Pace Conference, 37 items. (Box 16, Folder 602)
      - Pacific Westbound Conference, 74 items. (Box 16, Folder 603)